[

](https://webo.hosting/)
======================================================================================================================================================================================================================================

    **Web Hosting**  
    Linux web hosting

    **Wordpress Hosting**  
    Great for Wordpress

    **Website Builder**   
    Build a simple website

    **Reseller Hosting**  
    Sell your own web hosting

    **Windows Hosting**  
    Windows web hosting

    **Linux VPS**  
    Linux private server

    **Windows VPS  
    **Private Windows server

    **Dedicated  
    **Full flagged dedicated 

    **Nextcloud**

    **Cloud Admin** Admin & unlimited users

    **Cloud Single** Single user

    **Cloud Secure** Single user & Encryption

    **Cloud VPS** Virtual private server cloud

    **Dedicated server** Private dedicated server
    
    **Owncloud**

    **Cloud Admin** Admin & unlimited users

    **Cloud VPS** Virtual private server cloud

    **Dedicated server** Private dedicated server
    
    **Addons**

    **Free Single account** Free 5GB cloud storage

    **Servers**

    **Dedicated Server**  
    Your own dedicated server
    
    **Security**

    **SSL Certificates**  
    Secure your website
    
    **Services**

    **Managed Server**  
    Managing Server for you
    
    **Office & Documents**

    **Collabora Online**  
    Document server for Collabora

    **OnlyOffice**  
    Document Server for OnlyOffice
    
    **Email**

    **Email hosting**  
    Private email service

    **Zimbra**  
    Private email service & Cloud
    
    **Tools & Utilities** 

    **Whois domain**  
    Lookup domain details

    **Contact**  
    Have a question?

    **FAQ**  
    Frequently Asked Questions

    **Knowledgebase**  
    Tutorial & help in one place

    **Support tickets**  
    Support form our team

Privacy Policy
==============

1. [Home](https://webo.hosting/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective date: October 24, 2020**

WEBO GROUP ltd (“us”, “we”,  “our”, or “Provider”) operates the https://webo.hosting website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://webo.hosting

Definitions
-----------

### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

### Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Client

The Client is the individual using our Service. The Client corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### User

The User is the individual, listed in Client’s sub-account and can be employee, agent or representative of a Client, who primarily uses the restricted areas of client area for the purpose of accessing the Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Contact

The Contact is the individual, listed in Client’s sub-account and has no access to our systems. It is primarily used for purposes of providing Personal Data to the other service providers (like domain registrars). The Contact corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Visitor

The Visitor is the individual other than a User, who uses our websites, but has no access to restricted areas (where access requires logging in).

What data we collect
--------------------

We collect different types of information from or through the Service. The legal bases for us to process personal data are primarily that the processing is necessary for providing the Service in accordance with Webo.hosting’s Terms of Service and that the processing is carried out in our legitimate interests, which are further explained in the section “How do we use collected data” of this Policy. We may also process data upon your consent, asking for it as appropriate.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Cookies and Usage Data
* proof of ID (needed in some cases and is not saved permanently)

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you, but only if you have opted in during the registration process. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send, by opt out in our client area or by contacting us.

#### Personal Data collected by Client

A Client may store additional Personal Data under sub-account(s) in our client area. We have no direct relationship with individuals whose Personal Data it hosts as part of Client data. Each Client is responsible for providing information to its customers and third persons concerning the purpose for which Client collects their Personal Data and how this Personal Data is processed in or through the Service. Client is responsible for proper permissions set up for the User or sub-account.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

You can find more details about cookies on “[Cookie Policy](https://webo.hosting/en/cookie-policy/ "Cookie policy")” page.

How do we use collected data
----------------------------

We use the collected Personal Data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To billing and account maintenance details
* To provide customer support
* To monitor the usage of our Service
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues
* To provide services
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information unless you have opted not to receive such information
* To protect Provider’s intellectual property

We use the Non-Personal Data gathered from Visitors on our website in an aggregated form to get a better understanding of where our visitors come from and to help us better design and organise our website. Such data does not point to any individual person.

Retention of Data
-----------------

WEBO GROUP ltd will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

WEBO GROUP ltd will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

Transfer Of Data
----------------

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

WEBO GROUP ltd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data
------------------

### Business Transaction

If WEBO GROUP ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, WEBO GROUP ltd may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

WEBO GROUP ltd may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of WEBO GROUP ltd
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

Security Of Personal Data
-------------------------

Your Personal Data is held on secure servers hosted by us. The nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via the Internet. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. However, we will take all reasonable steps (including appropriate technical and organisational measures) to protect your Personal Data.

Data Security
-------------

WEBO GROUP ltd hosts its infrastructure in EU region, ISO 27001 certified and GDPR compliant data centers.

Backups are always kept on dedicated servers in different location from production servers.

“Do Not Track” Signals
----------------------

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

Your Rights
-----------

WEBO GROUP ltd aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

* To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
* To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
* To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to WEBO GROUP ltd. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

Service Providers
-----------------

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Domain registration

In order to process and validate domain registrations there may be a requirement to collect additional personal information such as utility bills, passport, drivers license, etc. This is a requirement of the registry in question and that data is then forwarded to the registry by us as part of the application process. After successfull domain registration we then purge any such data from our own systems immediately. All current domain registry applications require an email address, applicant name, applicant address, country of origin, phone number as part of the registration process and this information is made widely available in the public WHOIS database. This is a contractual requirement of the governing body ICANN, but is currently being reviewed by a number of interested parties including the EU commission, registries and registrars. WHOIS privacy can be used to obfuscate that information from the public WHOIS datastore.

### Fraud prevention

In order to circumvent fraud when registering for our products, we have policies in place to validate orders. In case order needs manual checking, we might ask you for proof of ID such as copy of a passport before processing the order. Any personal information supplied to us to validate an order is deleted or redacted within 72 hours.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Websites (not Services).

* **Google Analytics (only our Website)** Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the visits of our Websites. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
* **Piwik or Matomo** Piwik or Matomo is a web analytics service. You can visit their Privacy Policy page here: [https://matomo.org/privacy-policy](https://matomo.org/privacy-policy)

### Behavioral Remarketing

WEBO GROUP ltd uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits only to our Websites.

* **Google AdWords** Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads.](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

* **PayPal or Braintree** Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)
* **Stripe** Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/en-si/privacy](https://stripe.com/en-si/privacy)

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Intellectual property
---------------------

Provider does not give or transfer the Client any rights to intellectual property that is not in his possession.

All rights to the software used during the process of service provision are protected and belong to the Provider or the Provider is authorized to use them.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By email: privacy@webo.hosting

Recent changes:  
**24.10.2020**  
_A company name change to WEBO GROUP ltd_  

**Old Original statement:**  
_A-com, spletne storitve_ **New Changed statment:**  
_WEBO GROUP ltd_

[

](#)
========================================================================================================================================================================================

Web hosting, VPS, domain and SSL. Fast and reliable web hosting, VPS, domains and much more at crazy prices!

All our services are Google/Azure/AWS free! Every server is built by us from scratch and completely under our control.

* * *

* * *

Contact Us:  

info@webo.hosting

[

](#)
==================================================================================================================================================================================

Hosting
=======

Domain
======

Legals
======

Support
=======

Webo Network
============

Webo.Hosting
============

© 2022 Webo Hosting. All rights reserved -  All prices are in EUR and include VAT and discounts!

We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.

You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings.

Accept

Change cookie settings

Close GDPR Cookie Settings

* Privacy Overview
* Strictly Necessary Cookies
* 3rd Party Cookies

Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.

Strictly Necessary Cookies

Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.

Enable or Disable Cookies 

If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.

3rd Party Cookies

This website uses Google Analytics to collect anonymous information such as the number of visitors to the site, and the most popular pages.

Keeping this cookie enabled helps us to improve our website.

Enable or Disable Cookies 

Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences!

Enable All Save Settings
